(Bernadette:)Don't talk like that
on your wedding day.
Sorry, Ma... Bernadette.
Ma... Bern... You're my Bernadette.
- Good move telling Sheldon.
- Can't propose, can't talk to my friends.
(Leonard:)Is there anything else
I'm not allowed to do?
(Amy:)All right, that's enough.
Today is not about you two.
(Amy:)Today is about Howard
and Bernadette and me.
Folks, can I have your attention?
It's 5:00.
We're gonna take three more couples.
The rest have to come back
on Monday.
(Amy:)- No.
- I got this.
(Howard:)Excuse me, but is there any way
you can squeeze us in?
(Howard:)See, I'm an astronaut
and I'm leaving for Russia on Sunday...
(Howard:)...so I can take a Soyuz rocket
to the lnternational Space Station.
(Registrar:)Yeah, me too. I'll see you there.
(Bernadette:)I can't believe
we're not gonna get married.
I'm gonna go see if the couple at the
front of the line needs a maid of honor.